What makes you so happy
무엇이 당신을 그렇게 행복하게 만드는가
Is it that obvious?
그렇게 뻔한가요?
Changed gender
성별이 변경됨
Know the useless things
쓸데없는 것을 알아라
Gonna return it
돌려줄게
What should I return if I return it?
반품할 경우 무엇을 반품해야 하나요?
That one
하나
I didn't return it
나는 그것을 돌려주지 않았다
It should be Sister Shuyi who has withdrawn it, right?
철회한 사람은 슈이 자매여야겠죠?
Zheng Shuyi
정수이
Why did she quit anyway?
그런데 그녀는 왜 그만뒀나요?
That's what happened last time
지난번에 그런 일이 있었어
I found that I seemed to have misunderstood her
나는 그녀를 오해한 것 같다는 것을 깨달았다
So I just want to make it up to her.
그래서 나는 단지 그녀에게 화해하고 싶습니다.
I bought her some clothes
나는 그녀에게 옷을 사줬어요
She shouldn't have said she wanted to quit then
그때 그 사람이 그만두고 싶다고 말하지 말았어야 했는데
I won't let it
나는 그것을 허락하지 않을 것이다
Unexpectedly, she quit all the time.
예기치 않게 그녀는 항상 그만 두었습니다.
So she took the clothes
그래서 그녀는 옷을 가져갔어
I'm going back
나는 돌아갈 것이다
This number is called one point
이 숫자를 1포인트라고 합니다.
You are
당신은
Tomorrow, you
내일, 당신
But Sister Shuyi
그런데 슈이 언니
really love work
일을 정말 좋아해요
She received short notice yesterday
그녀는 어제 짧은 통지를 받았습니다
I went on a business trip this morning
오늘 아침에 출장을 갔어요
honestly
솔직히
she is alone
그녀는 혼자이다
Write an outline for interviews and business trips
면접이나 출장에 대한 개요를 작성하세요
it is really hard
정말 어렵다
do not know either
둘 다 모른다
Where does she get the motivation?
그녀는 어디서 동기를 얻나요?
She is on a business trip
그녀는 출장중이다
Left in the morning
아침에 떠났다
Good progress on the Le'an side
Le'an 측의 좋은 진전
Work is progressing in an orderly manner
작업은 순조롭게 진행되고 있습니다
banquet
연회
Is your phone broken?
휴대폰이 고장났나요?
why don't you contact me
왜 나에게 연락하지 않니?
I have posted so many posts on Moments
Moments에 너무 많은 게시물을 게시했습니다.
So many beautiful pictures
아름다운 사진이 너무 많아요
No appreciation at all
전혀 감사하지 않습니다.
No likes either
좋아요도 없음
Which hotel are you staying in?
어느 호텔에 묵고 계시나요?
which room
어느 방
Beauty
아름다움
why did you come
왜 왔어?
I'm on a business trip for a colleague
나는 동료를 위해 출장 중입니다
You are not easy
넌 쉽지 않아
Are you doing out-of-town news?
시외 뉴스를 하고 있나요?
and
그리고
There are so many people waiting for you
당신을 기다리는 사람들이 너무 많아요
Shanshan
산산
Is there something wrong with you?
당신에게 무슨 문제가 있나요?
No
아니요
I'm just tired of playing
그냥 놀다가 지쳤어
Can't you wait for two days?
이틀만 기다리면 안 되나요?
You
너
Wouldn't it be better to find someone to settle down with?
함께 정착할 사람을 찾는 것이 더 낫지 않을까요?
temporary stability
일시적인 안정성
That's not stability
그건 안정성이 아니잖아
some feelings
어떤 감정
Even if you settle down, you will still lose it.
정착하더라도 여전히 잃을 것입니다.
This kind of stability for me
나에겐 이런 안정감이
The risk factor is too high
위험요소가 너무 높음
how
어떻게
Shi Yan hasn’t contacted you yet
Shi Yan은 아직 연락하지 않았습니다.
No
아니요
You said it cost several thousand dollars?
몇천만원이 든다고 하던데요?
a mobile phone
핸드폰
Why is there even a little red dot?
왜 작은 빨간 점이 있는 걸까요?
None are displayed
아무것도 표시되지 않습니다
Hello
안녕하세요
Where are you
어디세요
Same place
같은 장소
I'm not in Jiangcheng
나 강성엔 없어
Then when will you come back?
그럼 언제 돌아올 거예요?
do not know yet
아직 몰라
Stop talking, my friend is sleeping
말 좀 그만해 친구가 자고 있어
Shanshan
산산
Snowing
강설
It's really snowing
눈이 정말 많이 오네요
The snow scene in Wucheng is so beautiful
우청의 설경이 너무 아름다워요
This is too much fun to miss Shu.
슈를 놓치기에는 너무 재미있다.
I was watching the last time you took me to the racecourse
지난번에 당신이 나를 경마장에 데려갔을 때 나는 보고 있었어요
That little girl?
그 어린 소녀?
Very generous
매우 관대함
This little girl is quite interesting
이 어린 소녀는 꽤 흥미로워요
Why haven't you seen her recently?
왜 최근에 그녀를 보지 못했나요?
She is on a business trip
그녀는 출장중이다
I saw her interviewing you.
나는 그녀가 당신을 인터뷰하는 것을 보았습니다.
that article
그 기사
This is really well written
이거 진짜 잘 썼네
This little girl is not old
이 어린 소녀는 늙지 않았습니다
This power is quite considerable
이 위력은 꽤 상당하다
This article is well written
이 글은 잘 쓰여졌네요
Sharper than many veteran reporters
많은 베테랑 기자들보다 날카로워
The writing is quite to the point.
글은 아주 요점에 충실합니다.
Yeah
응
I remember you before
예전에 당신을 기억해요
Not that I dislike talking to the media the most
내가 언론과 대화하는 것을 가장 싫어하는 것은 아니다.
Dealing with you?
당신을 상대하고 있나요?
People always have to make progress
사람은 항상 발전해야 한다
Now Yunchuang is on the rise
이제 Yunchuang이 상승세를 보이고 있습니다.
need to go through media
언론을 통해야 해
To let the public know more about Yunchuang
대중에게 Yunchuang에 대해 더 많이 알리기 위해
Good thing, good thing
좋은 일이야, 좋은 일이야
Next time you treat this little girl
다음에 이 어린 소녀를 치료할 때는
please come to home
집에 와주세요
I want to follow this one
이거 따라해보고싶다
Journalists who can change your mind
당신의 생각을 바꿀 수 있는 언론인
have a good chat
좋은 대화를 나누세요
come in
올
past past past
과거 과거 과거
Stand still, stand still
가만히 있어, 가만히 있어
Make a nice move
좋은 움직임을 만드십시오
What for?
무엇 때문에?
Leave it alone and listen to me
놔두고 내 말 좀 들어봐
Good to change
바꿔서 좋음
alright
괜찮은
Why do you post on Moments for me?
왜 나를 위해 Moments에 게시물을 올리나요?
Does it look good?
괜찮아 보이나요?
You won’t even let me fix it before sending it out.
보내기 전에 고치도록 허락하지도 않을 거예요.
so beautiful
너무 아름다워
Do I still need to improve my photography skills?
그래도 사진 기술을 향상시켜야 합니까?
Believe me
나를 믿어
Shiyan will come to you soon
Shiyan이 곧 당신에게 올 것입니다
I think your idea is fine
내 생각엔 네 생각이 좋은 것 같아
But give due consideration
하지만 충분히 고려해보세요
outside view
외부 모습
your abilities
당신의 능력
One day it will be proven
언젠가는 증명되겠죠
But before proving
하지만 증명하기 전에
There is nothing wrong with compromising and being diplomatic.
타협하고 외교하는 것은 잘못된 것이 아닙니다.
yes
예
its me
나야
Get to know these old guys
이 늙은이들을 알아보세요
they have all experienced
그 사람들 다 경험해 봤지
Mingyu’s best moments
민규의 최고의 순간들
What do you do to make money?
돈을 벌기 위해 무엇을 합니까?
Got some confidence
자신감 좀 얻었어요
A few years ago
몇 년 전
Mingyu's vitality was severely damaged
민규의 생명력이 심하게 손상되었습니다
They still have feelings for each other
그들은 여전히 ​​서로에 대한 감정을 갖고 있다.
No reduction
감소 없음
Nor did he sit idly by.
그는 가만히 앉아 있지도 않았습니다.
now you stand out
이제 당신이 눈에 띕니다
where are they
그들은 어디에 있나요?
You should also think about getting your blood back
혈액을 다시 채취하는 방법도 생각해야 합니다.
Urgent is a little too urgent
긴급은 좀 너무 긴급하다
But
하지만
No bad intentions
나쁜 의도는 없어요
I see
알겠어요
So I think more about it
그래서 더 생각이 나네요
Can't let their investment
그들의 투자를 놔둘 수는 없다
Any mistakes
어떤 실수라도
I heard about Chuxue’s wish
Chuxue???의 소원을 들었어
It will definitely come true
반드시 실현될 거예요
Snowing
강설
I don’t know how to wear more clothes.
옷을 더 입는 방법을 모르겠어요.
It looks like he was really playing
진짜 놀고 있었던 것 같다
Can't bear to come back
돌아오는 걸 견딜 수 없어
Shanshan
산산
You are too awesome, right?
당신은 너무 대단해요, 그렇죠?
When will we return to Jiangcheng?
우리는 언제 강성으로 돌아갈 것인가?
His cell phone was repaired
그의 휴대폰이 수리됐다
What to say
무슨 말을하는
I miss you
보고 싶어요
He misses you
그는 너를 그리워 해
What's the rush?
서두르는 이유는 무엇입니까?
Come back later
나중에 다시 오세요
What if he has a meeting soon?
곧 회의가 있으면 어쩌지?
what to do
무엇을 해야할지
There will always be a time when the meeting is over
항상 회의가 끝나는 시간이 있습니다
He has responded to you
그 분이 당신에게 응답하셨습니다.
You should be more reserved.
당신은 좀 더 신중해야합니다.
That seems like
그런 것 같아요
It's like you can't wait
마치 넌 기다릴 수 없는 것 같아
give him some
그에게 좀 줘
A sense of distance
거리감
Let him discover your specialness
그 사람이 당신의 특별함을 발견하게 해주세요
and precious
그리고 소중하다
Then when will I return?
그럼 난 언제 돌아올까?
Not urgent
긴급하지 않음
What should I reply to?
뭐라고 대답해야 하나요?
Just go back
그냥 돌아가세요
how do you know
어떻게 알아?
I'm not in Jiangcheng
나 강성엔 없어
That must have been seen
그건 본 게 틀림없어
I’m in the circle of friends
나는 친구 그룹에 속해 있어요
Then let him say it
그럼 그 사람이 말하게 놔둬
no
아니요
This person is Shi Yan
이 사람이 시얀이에요
you don't understand at all
당신은 전혀 이해하지 못합니다
I don’t understand the style at all
스타일이 전혀 이해가 안가네요
Maybe he doesn't like it at all
어쩌면 그 사람은 전혀 좋아하지 않을지도 몰라
This feeling of being far away
멀게만 느껴지는 이 느낌
okay, I get it
알았어, 알겠어
Just your seductive skills
그냥 당신의 매혹적인 기술
I don't think it's anything at all
전혀 별거 아닌 것 같은데
The banquet is incomprehensible
연회는 이해할 수 없다
It's you who have no charm
매력이 없는 건 너야
Uncle Guan wants to see you
관아저씨가 보고싶다
Uncle Guan
관 삼촌
Which uncle Guan
어느 관삼촌
Does it matter who Uncle Guan is?
관삼촌이 누구인지가 중요합니까?
This sentence
이 문장
You have to keep an eye on your uncle and see you
삼촌을 감시하고 만나야 해
Take off a piece
한 조각 떼어내다
want to see your person
당신의 사람을 보고 싶어요
It's not Uncle Guan at all.
관삼촌은 전혀 아닙니다.
It’s the president of Shiyanshi
시얀시 사장이네
What kind of pot goes with what kind of lid?
어떤 냄비에 어떤 뚜껑이 어울리나요?
Kindergarten level like you
너 같은 유치원 수준
Level of teasing
놀리는 수준
You have to live with this awkwardness
이 어색함을 안고 살아야 해
A boring man
지루한 남자
Shanshan
산산
Uncle Guan is Guan Xiangcheng
관삼촌은 관향성(Guan Xiangcheng)이다.
Shi Yan called Guan Xiangcheng Uncle Guan
Shi Yan은 Guan Xiangcheng을 Guan 삼촌이라고 불렀습니다.
Guan Xiangcheng
관샹청
Mr. Shi
시 씨
Don't whet my appetite
내 식욕을 자극하지 마세요
Say it quickly, say it quickly
빨리 말해 빨리 말해
Uncle Guan is willing to accept it
Guan 삼촌은 기꺼이 그것을 받아들입니다.
your interview
당신의 인터뷰
Thank you, boss. Thank you, boss.
감사합니다 보스. 감사합니다 보스.
Give the boss a leg pinch
사장님 다리 꼬집어주세요
You can come back
넌 돌아올 수 있어
OK, OK
그래 그래
I will be right back
곧 돌아올게요
I can give it to Guan Xiangcheng
Guan Xiangcheng에게 줄 수 있어요
Did an interview
인터뷰를 했어요
Oh my god
맙소사
Am I dreaming
저 꿈꾸고 있나요
Interview by Guan Xiangcheng
Guan Xiangcheng의 인터뷰
I was actually able to interview
실제로 인터뷰를 할 수 있었어요
The legendary Guan Xiangcheng
전설적인 관샹청(Guan Xiangcheng)
its not right
그것은 옳지 않아
when do i apply
내가 언제 신청해?
Interview by Guan Xiangcheng
Guan Xiangcheng의 인터뷰
So I just said
그래서 내가 방금 말했지
It's time for Yanyan to want you to go back
이제 Yanyan이 당신이 돌아가길 바라는 시간입니다
He must miss you
그 사람이 당신을 그리워할 거에요
I can't think of it anymore
더 이상 생각이 나지 않아요
That’s why I suddenly sent you a message
그래서 내가 갑자기 너한테 메시지를 보낸 거야
Uncle Guan
관 삼촌
That's just what he wants you to do
그 사람이 당신에게 바라는 게 바로 그거예요
An excuse to return to Jiangcheng as soon as possible
가능한 한 빨리 강성으로 돌아가려는 핑계
excuse
변명
Then I have to book a flight quickly
그럼 빨리 비행기 예약해야지
Make this interview a reality
이 인터뷰를 현실로 만들어 보세요
Zheng Shuyi
정수이
You can still have this kind of reserve, right?
아직도 이런 종류의 예비금을 가질 수 있습니다. 그렇죠?
Shanshan
산산
That's Guan Xiangcheng
관샹청이에요
I can be reserved
예약할 수 있어요
But my professionalism
하지만 내 전문성은
I'm not allowed to be reserved
예약이 안 돼요
There will be an interview tomorrow
내일 면접이 있어요
Hurry up and outline the interview today
오늘 빨리 인터뷰 개요를 작성해 보세요
Driven out
쫓겨나다
I'm back
나는 돌아왔다
quite early
꽤 일찍
Why are you still acting so weird?
왜 아직도 이상한 짓을 하는 거야?
Do you really think that I left Jiangcheng?
정말 내가 강성을 떠났다고 생각하시나요?
too long
너무 오래
He misses me
그 사람은 나를 그리워해요
can't wait to see me
나를 보고 싶어요
impossible
불가능한
I'm thinking too much
생각이 너무 많아
See you later
나중에 봐요
okay, I get it
알았어, 알겠어
I made an appointment with reporter Zheng for an interview
정 기자와 인터뷰 약속을 잡았습니다
You came earlier than others
남들보다 일찍 오셨군요
I'm not doing this for
나는 이것을 위해 이것을하는 것이 아닙니다
Come and learn from Uncle Guan?
관삼촌에게 와서 배우시겠어요?
Of course you can't be late
물론 늦으면 안 돼요.
Okay, okay, okay, won’t I expose you?
알았어 알았어 알았어 내가 널 폭로하지 않을래?
It's great to be young
젊다는게 참 좋은데
What's wrong, master?
무슨 일이에요, 선생님?
He's chasing me from behind
그 사람이 뒤에서 나를 쫓아오고 있어요
Girl, please wait a moment
아가씨, 잠시만 기다려주세요
How did you drive?
어떻게 운전하셨나요?
can you drive
운전할 수 있어?
I drive at normal speed
나는 보통 속도로 운전한다.
you suddenly slowed down
너 갑자기 속도가 느려졌어
Just bumped into
방금 우연히 마주쳤어요
I also drive normally
나도 평소에 운전한다
It was you who chased me
나를 쫓아온 건 바로 너였어
I just stopped
방금 멈췄어요
Okay, you two, stop arguing.
알았어, 둘 다 말다툼은 그만둬.
Wait until the traffic police and insurance company arrive
교통경찰과 보험회사가 도착할 때까지 기다리세요
Wait for them to investigate
그들이 조사할 때까지 기다리세요
I do not care
난 상관 없어
It's your responsibility
그것은 당신의 책임입니다
It's useless for anyone to come
누가 와도 소용없어
Uncle Guan is waiting for you
관아저씨가 당신을 기다리고 있어요
I'm sorry
죄송합니다
I am coming over now
나 지금 오고 있어
My problem?
내 문제?
Is this my problem
이게 내 문제인가?
Whose problem do you think it is?
누구의 문제라고 생각하시나요?
Slow ahead
천천히
What happened to you?
당신에게 무슨 일이 일어났나요?
My problem?
내 문제?
The car I was riding in was rear-ended
내가 타고 있던 차는 뒷바퀴였어
Processing now
지금 처리중
You're not hurt, are you?
당신은 다치지 않았죠?
I'm fine
잘 지내요
give me the address
주소 좀 알려줘
I'll ask Chen Sheng to pick you up
Chen Sheng에게 데리러 와달라고 부탁할게요
good
좋은
I have no quality
품격이 없어
I think you have no quality
내 생각엔 넌 자질이 없는 것 같아
What is your name
이름이 뭐에요
Wang Zhong
왕종
And you
당신은요
Yang Feifan
양페이판
Chen Sheng
첸 셩
I'm sorry
죄송합니다
wait for me a little longer
조금만 더 기다려줘
How did you come
어떻게 오셨나요?
Are you injured?
부상당하셨나요?
I'm fine
잘 지내요
What for?
무엇 때문에?
This car is a new energy vehicle
이 자동차는 새로운 에너지 자동차입니다
It seems there is something wrong with the battery
배터리에 문제가 있는 것 같습니다.
Battery
배터리
The car's battery
자동차 배터리
It’s from Zhanlan Technology
Zhanlan Technology의 제품입니다.
Recently, this blue technology
최근에는 이 블루테크
Aren't you raising money?
돈을 모으고 있지 않습니까?
I'm following this news
나는 이 소식을 팔로우하고 있다
So I want to know more about it
그래서 그것에 대해 더 알고 싶어요.
Or there will be unexpected gains
아니면 예상치 못한 이익이 생길 것입니다.
I'll go with you
나는 당신과 함께 갈 것이다
Traffic police comrades
교통경찰 동지들
Recently, this new energy vehicle
최근에는 이 신에너지 차량이
Are there many similar accidents?
비슷한 사고가 많나요?
Not much
별로
There must have been a few cases
몇 가지 경우가 있었을 텐데요.
Sorry, Comrade Traffic Police
죄송합니다 교통경찰 동지님
Excuse me
실례합니다
Is this accident related to the battery?
이번 사고는 배터리와 관련이 있나요?
This is not sure
확실하지 않습니다
This needs to be professionally tested
이건 전문가의 테스트가 필요해요
Only then can we draw conclusions
그래야만 결론을 내릴 수 있다
You two are passengers, right?
너희 둘은 승객이구나, 그렇지?
It's taken care of now
지금은 처리됐어
If nothing happens
아무 일도 일어나지 않으면
You can go
당신은 갈 수 있습니다
Thanks
감사해요
thank you
감사합니다
fine
괜찮은
Oops, late.
이런, 늦었어요.
I forgot to talk to Mr. Guan
관 씨와 얘기하는 걸 깜빡했어요
Say it
말해
we have to hurry up
우리는 서둘러야 해
Don't keep him waiting too long
그를 너무 오래 기다리게 하지 마세요
Enter
입력하다
Editor-in-Chief
편집장
What's wrong, Yu Ling?
무슨 일이야, 유 링?
I contacted three companies
3개 회사에 연락했어요
vice president of commercial bank
상업은행 부행장
they promised me
그들은 나에게 약속했다
We can do an exclusive interview together
독점 인터뷰를 함께 할 수 있어요
i want to ask you
나는 당신에게 묻고 싶습니다
help me this month
이번 달에 나 좀 도와줘
The front page remains
앞페이지가 남아있습니다
The three vice presidents conducted interviews together
부사장 3명이 함께 인터뷰를 진행했다.
OK
좋아요
This interview is important
이 인터뷰가 중요해요
It must be on the front page
맨 앞 페이지에 있어야 합니다.
Thank you editor-in-chief
편집장님께 감사드립니다
Yuling
율링
you have always been us
당신은 항상 우리였습니다
Financial agency’s sign
금융 기관???의 표시
Professional ability is also very strong
전문적인 능력도 매우 강하다
The editor-in-chief and I are very optimistic about you.
편집장과 나는 당신에 대해 매우 낙관적입니다.
Keep up the good work
계속해서 좋은 일을 하세요
Thank you editor-in-chief
편집장님께 감사드립니다
Then I'll get busy first
그럼 나 먼저 바빠질게
Sister Yi
이 자매
I won’t go back to the magazine yet.
나는 아직 잡지로 돌아가지 않을 것이다.
My interview today about Xiang Cheng
오늘 Xiang Cheng에 대한 인터뷰
Interview by Guan Xiangcheng
Guan Xiangcheng의 인터뷰
I see
알겠어요
Good luck to you
행운을 빕니다
Hello
안녕하세요
Why are you free during working hours?
근무시간에는 왜 시간이 없나요?
Call me
전화해
That's of course because
물론 그 이유는
what i want to say to you
내가 너에게 하고 싶은 말
related to work
일과 관련된
I won't call Mr. Guan personally
관 씨에게 개인적으로 전화하지 않겠습니다
how to be sure
어떻게 확신할 수 있나요?
Our financial agency
우리 금융기관
Are you really asking for help?
정말 도움을 요청하는 건가요?
Your great Buddha has come out of the mountain.
당신의 위대한 부처님이 산에서 나오셨습니다.
Reporter Zheng told you, right?
정 기자가 말했지요?
I made an appointment with her today
나 오늘 그 사람이랑 약속했어
Come and have a chat
와서 채팅을 해보세요
How did she find you?
그녀가 당신을 어떻게 찾았나요?
its me
나야
I have read several of her masterpieces
나는 그녀의 걸작을 여러 권 읽었습니다.
This is young
이것은 젊다
His writing skills are really impressive.
그의 글쓰기 능력은 정말 인상적이다.
This writing is so sharp and reasonable
글이 너무 날카롭고 합리적이네요
What a terrible future life!
정말 끔찍한 미래의 삶입니다!
So I let a nephew
그래서 조카를 보내줬어요
Invite her to come and sit at home
그녀를 집에 초대하여 집에 앉으십시오
That's natural
그건 당연해요
Shuyi is my right-hand man
Shuyi는 내 오른팔이야
Professional capabilities in our magazine
우리 잡지의 전문적인 능력
It's also one of the best
그것도 최고 중 하나야
Her understanding and sensitivity are very high
이해도와 감수성이 매우 높다
So text
그래서 문자
It’s also very powerful and angley
그것은 또한 매우 강력하고 각도가 높습니다.
I'm looking forward to it more and more
점점 더 기대되네요
This interview
이번 인터뷰
You two do
너희 둘은 그러지
Meeting each other’s expectations
서로의 기대에 부응하다
But it gave me a big trouble
하지만 그것은 나에게 큰 고민을 안겨주었다
Yes Yes Yes
예 예 예
It's because I didn't think carefully.
신중하게 생각하지 않았기 때문이다.
I didn't tell you in advance
미리 말 안 했는데
Have I caused trouble for you again?
내가 또 당신을 괴롭혔나요?
Like this
이와 같이
Me at night
나 밤에
I'll apologize to you personally
개인적으로 사과드리겠습니다
Can I pick you up after you get off work?
퇴근 후에 데리러 갈 수 있나요?
Do not bother
귀찮게 하지 마세요
I'll go there by myself tonight
오늘 밤엔 나 혼자 거기 갈 거야
See you tonight, see you tonight
오늘 밤에 봐요, 오늘 밤에 봐요
See you tonight
오늘 밤에 만나요
Uncle Guan
관 삼촌
Coming
오는
Come, come, come
어떻게, 어떻게, 어떻게
Sit, sit, sit, please.
앉아, 앉아, 앉아주세요.
Hello Mr. Guan
안녕하세요 관씨님
sit
앉다
Miss Zheng
미스 정
today
오늘
I should call you Reporter Zheng.
정 기자에게 전화해야겠습니다.
Be casual
캐주얼하게
You can be like Shi Yan
당신도 Shi Yan처럼 될 수 있어요
Just call me Uncle Guan
그냥 관아저씨라고 불러주세요
Don't see anyone outside
밖에는 아무도 보지 마세요
Don't see the outside, don't see the outside
밖을 보지 마세요, 밖을 보지 마세요
Today we
오늘 우리
Just chat casually
그냥 아무렇지도 않게 얘기해
I read some of your articles
나는 당신의 기사 중 일부를 읽었습니다.
I think it's well written
잘 쓴 것 같아요
There are many opinions
많은 의견이 있습니다
Very fresh
매우 신선함
Very thoughtful too
매우 사려 깊음
The angle is also very tricky
각도도 너무 까다로워요
You flatter me
당신은 나에게 아첨한다
Actually, what about me?
사실 나는 어떻습니까?
Haven't followed you for a long time
오랫동안 당신을 따르지 않았습니다
Except for seasonal banquets
계절 연회를 제외하고
The young people talked
젊은이들이 이야기했다.
So I invite you to come over today
그래서 오늘 당신을 이리로 초대합니다
Let's communicate
소통하자
Also let me, an old antique,
또한 오래된 골동품인 나에게도
Can be contacted
연락 가능
young minds
젊은 마음
progress progress
진행 진행
You are serious
진지 하구나
I should be the one asking you for advice
당신에게 조언을 구하는 사람은 나여야만 해요
It doesn't matter, it's all the same
상관없어 다 똑같아
Have a cup of tea first
먼저 차 한잔 드세요
This is what I treasure
이것이 내가 소중히 여기는 것
Most people don’t even drink it.
대부분의 사람들은 그것을 마시지도 않습니다.
I'm not good at drinking tea
나는 차를 잘 마시지 못한다.
I usually drink drinks
나는 평소에 음료수를 마신다.
Maybe the cow chewed the peony
어쩌면 소가 모란을 씹었을지도 몰라
You try it first
먼저 시도해 보세요.
Drink it you will like it
마셔보면 좋아할 거야
This is boiled in snow water
이것은 눈물에 삶아진 것입니다
What happened to the boiled snow?
끓인 눈은 어떻게 됐나요?
Don't you like snow?
눈이 싫으세요?
How do you know she likes snow?
그녀가 눈을 좋아한다는 것을 어떻게 알 수 있나요?
It was written in her circle of friends
그녀의 친구 서클에 쓰여 있었어
Is Shi Yan being in a weird mood?
시옌님 기분이 이상하신가요?
He just blamed me for being away for too long
그 사람은 내가 너무 오랫동안 떨어져 있었다고 비난했어
came back late
늦게 돌아왔다
Delicious and tastes like snow
맛있고 눈처럼 맛있어요
I love so much
나는 너무 사랑한다
Then let’s talk about business
그럼 사업 얘기 좀 하자
I go to the yard
나는 마당으로 간다
Then let's get started, Mr. Guan
그럼 시작하겠습니다, 관 씨
good
좋은
It's hard to imagine
상상하기 힘들다
My first pot of gold
내 첫 번째 금 냄비
That's four hundred and thirty-five yuan
435위안이에요
it's hard to imagine it
상상하기 힘들다
It's us now
이제 우리야
Kwan Capital
관캐피탈
Oh my god
맙소사
Amazing
놀라운
Zheng Shuyi
정수이
Be more restrained
좀 더 자제하세요
Uncle Guan
관 삼촌
time to eat
먹을 시간
I had a great chat with Reporter Zheng
정 기자와 즐거운 대화를 나눴습니다
I forgot about this time
이번에는 잊어버렸어
Shi Yan, it’s better if you don’t tell me
시옌, 말하지 않는 게 나을 것 같아
Just say it
그냥 말해
I'm really a little hungry
나 사실 좀 배가 고파서
Mr. Kwan
씨. 관
It was a great pleasure chatting with you today
오늘 대화해서 정말 즐거웠어요
I will sort out the manuscript as soon as possible
최대한 빨리 원고를 정리하겠습니다.
Check it out for you
직접 확인해보세요
Then you can eat first
그럼 먼저 먹어도 돼
I won't bother you
난 당신을 귀찮게하지 않을 것입니다
The meal is on the table
식사는 식탁 위에 있어요
Leave after eating
식사 후 출발
He's not in a hurry
그 사람은 서두르지 않아요
What are you anxious about?
당신은 무엇에 대해 걱정하고 있습니까?
Have a meal
식사하세요
Come here
이리 오세요
How can this be so embarrassing?
이게 어떻게 그렇게 당황스러울 수 있나요?
Come and sit
와서 앉으세요
Miss Zheng
미스 정
How old are you this year?
올해 몇 살이신가요?
I'm twenty-five
나는 스물다섯 살이에요
Soon to be twenty-six years old
곧 스물다섯 살이 된다.
At that time, there was a feast of twenty-seven
그 당시에는 스물일곱 살의 잔치가 있었습니다.
Two years older than you
너보다 두 살 더 많아
You two are quite compatible in your zodiac signs.
두 사람은 조디악 표지판에서 꽤 호환됩니다.
I feel so too
나도 그렇게 느낀다
Come and have a meal
와서 식사하세요
a while
잠시
Are there any other arrangements?
다른 조치가 있나요?
Do you want to go to the racecourse again?
또 경마장에 가고 싶나요?
It's been a while since we both went there
우리 둘 다 거기 가본 지 꽤 됐어
I've always wanted to go again
늘 또 가고 싶었는데
The scenery of the racecourse
경마장의 풍경
refreshing
상쾌한
But I'm a little busy recently
그런데 요즘 좀 바빠서
There will be a chance in the future
앞으로도 기회가 있을 거예요
Must go again
다시 가야 해
when you want to go
네가 가고 싶을 때
Just go directly
그냥 직접 가세요
Right? Shiyan
오른쪽? 스옌
Thank you Uncle Guan
감사합니다 관아저씨
In the past two years, Shi Yan
지난 2년 동안 Shi Yan은
Fewer people go to the racecourse.
경마장에 가는 사람이 적습니다.
But he is familiar with them all
하지만 그는 그들 모두를 잘 알고 있습니다.
You went with him
그 사람이랑 같이 갔잖아
What can't you do?
당신은 무엇을 할 수 없습니까?
call him
그에게 전화
Did he often go to the racecourse before?
그 사람은 전에도 경마장에 자주 갔었나요?
After starting a business
사업을 시작한 후
he is very busy
그는 매우 바빠요
Fewer people go
가는 사람이 적다
When I was young
내가 어렸을 때
He goes every week
그 사람 매주 가는데
Mr. Shi has loved horse riding since he was a child.
Shi 씨는 어렸을 때부터 승마를 좋아했습니다.
When he was a child
그가 어렸을 때
What is it like
어떤가요?
I was sensible when I was a child
나는 어렸을 때 현명했다.
To myself
나에게
Always very demanding
항상 매우 까다로운
But a child
하지만 아이
No matter how calm and calm you are
아무리 침착하고 침착해도
He will always feel depressed
그는 항상 우울함을 느낄 것이다
and when you are unhappy
그리고 당신이 불행할 때
That's when he met
그 때 그 사람이 만났어요.
Unhappy thing
불행한 것
say nothing
아무 말도 하지 마세요
Not even telling his father
아버지한테도 말하지 않고
I just like going to the racecourse
나는 단지 경마장에 가는 것을 좋아한다.
Riding a horse around and around
말을 타고 여기저기 돌아다니다
He is now
그는 지금
I have the same personality as when I was a child
어릴때랑 성격이 똑같네
Don't want to say anything
아무 말도 하고 싶지 않아
then
그 다음에
Something happened to Mingyu
민규에게 무슨 일이 일어났나
disrupted his business plan
그의 사업 계획을 방해했다
He is
그는
The matter in Mingyu was handled well
민규 사건은 잘 처리됐어
about there
거기쯤
I just left to start Yunchuang
방금 Yunchuang을 시작하러 떠났습니다.
He personally took Mingyu
민규를 직접 데려갔어
Leave it to his brother-in-law
형부에게 맡겨라
This other person
이 다른 사람
Many people don't know the situation
상황을 모르는 사람들이 많네요
They all thought it was a seasonal banquet.
그들은 모두 그것이 계절적인 연회라고 생각했습니다.
avoid responsibility
책임을 회피하다
actually
실제로
He is better than anyone
그는 누구보다 낫다
All have a lot of responsibilities
모두들 책임이 많아요
Many sacrifices have been made
많은 희생이 있었습니다
Actually
실제로
others don't know
다른 사람들은 몰라
Where's the banquet?
연회는 어디에서 하나요?
It’s to take your own reputation
그것은 자신의 평판을 앗아가는 것입니다.
Leave it to him
그 사람에게 맡겨
The most suitable brother-in-law to take over
물려받기에 가장 적합한 처남
And him
그리고 그 사람
Always have ideals
항상 이상을 가지고
Also prepared for a long time
또한 오랫동안 준비한
so
그래서
Just founded this Yunchuang
방금 이 Yunchuang을 설립했습니다.
Just don't like to talk
그냥 얘기하는 걸 안 좋아하는 거야
I don’t even like to tell people my true feelings.
나는 사람들에게 내 진심을 말하는 것을 좋아하지도 않습니다.
After you're fine
괜찮다면
Talk to him more
그 사람과 더 얘기해 보세요
Correct this bad problem
이 나쁜 문제를 수정하세요
Don't keep everything in your heart
모든 것을 마음속에 담아두지 마세요
Uncle Guan
관 삼촌
The shrimp won’t taste good if it’s cold.
새우는 추우면 맛이 없어요.
Don't you want me to talk about him?
내가 그에 대해 이야기하는 것을 원하지 않나요?
okay
좋아요
Just let him tell you yourself
그 사람이 직접 말하게 놔두세요
But
하지만
Now Yunchuang is booming
지금 Yunchuang은 호황을 누리고 있습니다.
It can be considered as living up to his efforts.
그의 노력에 부응하는 것이라고 볼 수 있다.
There is still effort
아직 노력은 남아있어
What has he been thinking about these past two years?
지난 2년 동안 그는 무엇을 생각하고 있었나요?
Put it all on Yunchuang
모두 윤추앙에 맡겨라
There's not even time for falling in love
사랑에 빠질 시간조차 없어
Now in the industry
지금 업계에서는
Highly rated Yunchuang
높은 평점을 받은 Yunchuang
Projects selected by Yunchuang
Yunchuang이 선정한 프로젝트
It can also be reflected
반영되기도 합니다
Mr. Shi’s sense of social responsibility
Shi 씨의 사회적 책임감
and vision
그리고 비전
I believe Mr. Shi
나는 시 씨를 믿는다
will realize his ideal
그의 이상을 실현할 것이다
Miss Zheng
미스 정
You are also amazing
당신도 대단해요
little girl
어린 소녀
The journalist profession
언론인이라는 직업
I have come into contact with many
나는 많은 사람들과 접촉하게 되었다
former friends
옛 친구
Worked for many years
수년 동안 일했습니다.
In the end
결국
They all changed careers one after another.
그들은 모두 차례로 직업을 바꾸었습니다.
You are so young and have so many opportunities
넌 너무 어리고 기회도 많아
can persevere
인내할 수 있다
It's not easy
쉽지 않다
In fact, our magazine
사실 우리 잡지는
Mostly girls
대부분 소녀들
and
그리고
They're all pretty
다들 예뻐요
This looks good
이거 좋아 보이는데
That is also a kind of capital
그것도 일종의 자본이다.
Then when I was interviewed
그러다가 인터뷰를 했을 때
Who doesn't like it?
누가 그것을 좋아하지 않습니까?
Looks like this looks good-looking
이거 잘생겼나보네요
And then there is wisdom
그러면 지혜가 있느니라
Where is the beautiful reporter?
그 아름다운 기자는 어디에 있나요?
yes
예
Mr. Shi also likes it
시 선생님도 좋아해요
Very good-looking female reporter
정말 잘생긴 여자 기자
Right
오른쪽
Isn't it?
그렇지 않나요?
Participated with me last time
지난번에 저랑 같이 참여했어요
My colleague at the press conference
기자회견에 참석한 동료
You've been staring at this person for a long time
당신은 오랫동안 이 사람을 바라보고 있었습니다.
And what about this?
그리고 이건 어때요?
No
아니요
There is
있다
Auntie
이모
This pork rib is still a bit spicy.
이 돼지갈비는 아직 좀 매워요.
You process it again
다시 처리하시네요
You asked people later
나중에 사람들한테 물어봤잖아
Where have you gone?
어디 갔다?
I said I'm not feeling well and I'm going home first.
몸이 안 좋아서 먼저 집에 갈 거라고 했어요.
You still ask people where they feel uncomfortable?
아직도 사람들에게 어디가 불편한지 물어보시나요?
I'm teasing you
나는 당신을 놀리는 중입니다
real
진짜
how
어떻게
Do not believe
믿을 수 없어
Unfaithfulness
불성실함
So what do you have to do to believe it?
그러면 그것을 믿으려면 어떻게 해야 합니까?
I want to eat that
나는 그것을 먹고 싶다
I want to eat shrimp
새우 먹고싶다
Why don't you peel it off for me?
나를 위해 껍질을 벗기는 게 어때요?
I'll peel it off myself
내가 직접 벗겨볼게
for you
당신을 위한
boarding
탑승
nice weather today
오늘 날씨 좋다
The sun is so big
태양이 너무 커요
It’s so comfortable to tan
태닝하기 너무 편해요
What a day for exercise
운동하기 딱 좋은 날
What do you want to do?
뭐하고 싶어?
I don’t want to take a car and want to take a walk
차도 타기 싫고 산책도 하고 싶다
will you accompany me
나와 함께 갈래?
Zheng Shuyi
정수이
Now make heaven and earth
이제 하늘과 땅을 만들어라
I can't satisfy you anymore
더 이상 당신을 만족시킬 수 없어요
I not only make heaven and earth
나는 하늘과 땅을 만들 뿐만 아니라
I can also compose poetry
시도 쓸 수 있어요
you compose poetry
당신은시를 작곡
I don’t know the meaning of the book but Jiangcheng is far away
책의 의미는 모르지만 강성은 멀리 있다
The Shi family's small banquet was jealous of Xue
Shi 가족의 작은 연회는 Xue를 질투했습니다.
Zheng Shuyi
정수이
What's wrong? I'm not wrong.
뭐가 문제 야? 나는 틀리지 않았다.
right
오른쪽
you are right
당신 말이 맞아요
I didn’t expect my little poem
내 작은 시를 기대하진 않았어
How can I always be so happy when I get it?
그것을 받으면 어떻게 항상 그렇게 행복할 수 있나요?
I also prepared something else
또 다른 것도 준비했어요
Always happy when asking for help
도움을 요청할 때 항상 기뻐하십시오.
Do you always have to listen to it?
항상 들어야 하는 걸까요?
These days
요즘에는
I'm thinking hard
열심히 생각하고 있어요
I carefully prepared one for Mr. Shi
시 선생님을 위해 정성껏 준비했어요
Yunchuang’s special planning project
Yunchuang의 특별 기획 프로젝트
every punctuation mark
모든 구두점
I knocked them all with my own hands
내 손으로 다 두들겼어
fully expressed
완전히 표현됨
My interview with Mr. Shi and this interview
Shi 씨와의 인터뷰와 이번 인터뷰
Care and attention
배려와 관심
It's getting late. Come back quickly.
늦겠다. 빨리 돌아오세요.
nothing
아무것도 아님
Just word by word
그냥 한마디 한마디
Type this plan
이 계획을 입력하세요
My wrist is just a little sore
손목이 좀 아프네요
It's not a serious illness
심각한 질병은 아니죠
I can still bear it
아직은 견딜 수 있어
Can
할 수 있다
What can be
무엇이 될 수 있는가?
It's not you who do it
그런 짓을 하는 건 당신이 아니야
Yunchuang's special topic?
윤추앙의 특집은?
Can
할 수 있다
thank you
감사합니다
But I have two requirements
하지만 두 가지 요구 사항이 있습니다.
I agree to all two hundred requests.
나는 200개 요청 모두에 동의합니다.
First
첫 번째
You must follow the whole process
모든 과정을 따라야 합니다
and in-depth understanding of Yunchuang
Yunchuang에 대한 깊은 이해
and my daily work
그리고 내 일상 업무
and the specific situation of some projects
일부 프로젝트의 특정 상황
Especially my work ideas
특히 내 작업 아이디어
How does this sound?
어떻게 들리나요?
a bit strange
조금 이상하다
Then Reporter Zheng agreed
그러자 정 기자가 동의했다.
Still not agreeing
아직도 동의하지 않음
promise promise
약속 약속
Opportunity to get to know Mr. Shi deeply
시씨를 깊이 알아가는 기회
Of course I can't miss it
물론 놓칠 수는 없지
second
두번째
If the article is written in a biased way
기사가 편향적으로 작성된 경우
Or the writing is not profound enough
아니면 글이 충분히 심오하지 않은가?
I have the right to stop at any time
나는 언제든지 멈출 권리가 있다
This special topic
이 특별한 주제
so harsh
너무 가혹하다
Get in the car
차에 타라
I also agreed to the second request.
나는 두 번째 요청에도 동의했습니다.
Looking forward to cooperating with Yunchuang
Yunchuang과의 협력을 기대합니다.
I will never give it to you
난 절대 너한테 안 줄 거야
opportunity to call a halt
정지를 요청할 기회
Lao Fan
라오스 판
Send Reporter Zheng home first
정 기자를 먼저 집으로 보내라
I have other things to do
난 다른 할 일이 있어
OK
좋아요
Forget it, what's the rush?
잊어버리세요, 왜 서두르나요?
She doesn't know me yet
그 사람은 아직 나를 몰라요
Wait until she knows you well enough
그녀가 당신을 충분히 알게 될 때까지 기다리세요
that day
그 날
Make your decision again
다시 결정을 내리세요
goodbye
안녕히 가세요
Wucheng
우청
Dear travelers
친애하는 여행자
Heading to Jiangcheng
강성으로 향합니다
Flight MU5857
항공편 MU5857
Boarding begins
탑승 시작
What a coincidence to pick someone up?
누군가를 데리러 가는 것은 무슨 우연인가?
Yes, pick you up
응, 데리러 와
No?
아니요?
pick me up
나를 데리러
Long time no see, a little bit
오랜만이네, 조금은
miss you
보고 싶어요
I guess so
그런 것 같아요
The above is blue
위의 내용은 파란색입니다.
Business conditions in recent years
최근 몇 년간의 사업 상황
It is understood
이해된다
There are currently three car companies
현재 3개의 자동차 회사가 있습니다.
and two investment and financing companies
두 개의 투자 및 금융 회사
Expressed to Zhanlan
잔란에게 표현됨
clear willingness to cooperate
협력하겠다는 분명한 의지
Yunchuang wants and Zhanlan
Yunchuang은 원하고 Zhanlan은
If you cooperate
협조해 주시면
very intense competition
매우 치열한 경쟁
Mr. Shi
시 씨
You need to work harder
더 열심히 일해야 해
Yu You
유유
What do you think
어떻게 생각하나요
Solid-state batteries have high performance
전고체 배터리는 고성능을 가지고 있습니다.
Enhanced security features
강화된 보안 기능
It is indeed expected to become the future
정말 미래가 될 것으로 예상됩니다
Direction of development
개발방향
and hidden
숨겨진
Huge demand market
거대한 수요 시장
This is also consistent with
이는 또한 다음과 일치합니다.
The dual carbon plan implemented by the country
국가에서 시행하는 이중 탄소 계획
on this track
이 트랙에서
Zhan Lan is indeed a winner
Zhan Lan은 실제로 승자입니다
Consultant Yu’s analysis is very correct.
유 컨설턴트의 분석은 매우 정확합니다.
Zhanlan’s current production system
Zhanlan의 현재 생산 시스템
very mature
매우 성숙하다
If you invest
투자하면
Our risk is much less
우리의 위험은 훨씬 적습니다
but
하지만
competition is so fierce
경쟁이 너무 치열해요
It’s not the first two rounds of investment
처음 두 차례의 투자가 아닙니다.
This also means
이것은 또한 의미합니다
Yunchuang wants to eat this piece of meat
윤추앙은 이 고기 조각을 먹고 싶어
There may be a big price to pay
큰 대가를 치르게 될 수도 있다
However, the conclusion from the evaluation is that
그러나 평가의 결론은 다음과 같다.
There's something going on in this market
이 시장에 뭔가가 일어나고 있어요
Mr. Shi
시 씨
what do you think
어떻게 생각하나요
Everyone has noticed
다들 눈치채셨죠
What happened two days ago
이틀 전에 무슨 일이 있었나요?
New energy vehicle accident?
신에너지 자동차 사고?
Seems
것 같다
Hengxin new energy vehicle accident
헝신 신에너지 자동차 사고
That's what they use at home
그게 집에서 사용하는 거거든요
blue battery
파란색 배터리
clear blue
맑은 파란색
car accident
교통 사고
Isn't it normal?
정상이 아닌가요?
Moreover
게다가
Not necessarily
꼭 그런 것은 아니다
Is it a battery problem?
배터리 문제인가요?
Invest in any track
모든 트랙에 투자하세요
It's all an adventure
그것은 모두 모험이다
I still want to do more
아직은 더 하고 싶은데
Preparation
준비
Everyone said it just now
지금 다들 그렇게 말했지
Invest in blue
블루에 투자하세요
The competition itself is fierce
경쟁 자체가 치열해요
Azure is for Yunchuang
Azure는 Yunchuang을 위한 것입니다.
Definitely the best choice
확실히 최선의 선택
Mr. Shi
시 씨
i remember you before
난 예전에 당신을 기억해요
Aren’t you also very optimistic about Zhanlan?
당신도 Zhanlan에 대해 매우 낙관적이지 않나요?
I'm optimistic about
나는 낙관적이다
Is new energy essential to future life?
미래의 삶에 새로운 에너지가 꼭 필요한가?
and positive changes in the environment
그리고 환경의 긍정적인 변화
and enter this track
그리고 이 트랙으로 들어가세요
What it means to Yunchuang
윤추앙에게 그것은 무엇을 의미하는가
But the solid-state battery industry
하지만 전고체전지 산업은
Investment requires big bets
투자에는 큰 베팅이 필요합니다
Do more research and analysis
더 많은 연구와 분석을 수행하세요.
I think it's necessary
나는 그것이 필요하다고 생각한다.
But I heard
그러나 나는 들었다
During these two months
이 두 달 동안
they will draw conclusions
그들은 결론을 내릴 것이다
by that time
그때쯤이면
Which one to choose?
어느 것을 선택할까요?
Will it be too late?
너무 늦을까요?
yes
예
So many investment companies
투자회사가 너무 많아서
All bets have been placed
모든 베팅이 완료되었습니다.
There shouldn't be anything wrong with that, right?
거기에는 아무런 문제가 없어야 합니다. 그렇죠?
Big deal
큰 거래
Let's discuss it with each other
서로 토론해보자
Take a smaller share
더 작은 몫을 가져가세요
That's okay too
그것도 괜찮아
Mr. Shi
시 씨
I know you are cautious
당신이 조심스럽다는 걸 알아요
But investing in blue
그러나 파란색에 투자
This is an opportunity not to be missed
놓칠 수 없는 기회입니다
Tan Yong
탄용
Do another round of assessment
또 다른 평가를 수행하세요.
Then we'll see
그럼 보자
OK
좋아요
banquet
연회
What a clever trick you have
당신은 얼마나 영리한 속임수를 가지고 있습니까?
Now take the blue
이제 파란색을 가져가세요
It's really difficult
정말 어렵다
If you can get this
이것을 얻을 수 있다면
Everyone will think you are awesome
다들 당신이 대단하다고 생각할 거예요
Even if you can't win it in the end
결국 이기지 못하더라도
They won't say anything
그들은 아무 말도 하지 않을 거야
high
높은
Really high
정말 높다
This is from the evaluation department
평가부서에서 온 내용입니다
Written report
서면 보고서
You can take a look
살펴보실 수 있어요
New energy vehicles using this battery
이 배터리를 사용하는 신에너지 자동차
How many accidents happened
얼마나 많은 사고가 일어났는가
and some related
그리고 일부 관련
accident investigation report
사고 조사 보고서
This year alone
올해만은
So many accidents happened
사고가 너무 많이 났어요
But that doesn't mean anything
하지만 그건 아무 의미가 없어
Now new energy vehicles
이제 새로운 에너지 차량
Large usage base
대규모 사용 기반
probability of accident
사고 확률
Naturally big
당연히 크다
Oil trucks also have accident rates
석유트럭에도 사고율이 있다
Not necessarily less than new energy vehicles
반드시 신에너지 차량보다 낮을 필요는 없습니다.
you're right
네가 옳아
But the core issue now is
하지만 지금의 핵심 문제는
Although the blue market
블루마켓이지만
Very large share
매우 큰 점유율
But the batteries they use
하지만 그들이 사용하는 배터리는
It’s still last year’s technology
아직 작년의 기술인가요?
No updates so far
지금까지 업데이트가 없습니다
Orders are now liquidated
이제 주문이 청산되었습니다.
If they succeed in financing
펀딩에 성공하면
Must want to expand the scale
규모를 확장하고 싶음
continuously
계속해서
Increase market share
시장 점유율 증가
But in the long run
하지만 장기적으로는
technological breakthrough
기술적 혁신
That's the most important thing
그게 가장 중요한 거야
But if there is a problem with the battery
하지만 배터리에 문제가 있다면
Never solved
해결되지 않음
Accidents just keep happening
사고가 계속 일어나네요
Major car companies
주요 자동차 회사
Will also think of alternatives
대안도 생각해 볼 것
Then our investment is still not
그렇다면 우리의 투자는 아직
a safe investment
안전한 투자
Not necessarily
꼭 그런 것은 아니다
Zhanlan’s financing this time
이번에는 Zhanlan의 자금 조달
It’s already Series B
이미 시리즈 B입니다
Passed the angel round and A round
엔젤 라운드와 A 라운드를 통과했습니다.
In fact, to some extent
사실 어느 정도는
does not conform to
에 부합하지 않습니다
Yunchuang’s investment strategy
Yunchuang의 투자 전략
Although you can specialize in
전문적으로 할 수는 있어도
But like you said
하지만 당신이 말했듯이
Do another round of research
또 다른 연구를 해보세요
It's still necessary
여전히 필요해요
Our uncles
우리 삼촌들
Anxious to get the blue one
파란거 사려고 고민중
It's them too
그것도 그들이에요
Something's really going to happen
진짜 무슨 일이라도 일어날 거야
We should also blame our mistakes in judgment.
우리는 또한 우리의 판단 실수를 비난해야 합니다.
so
그래서
You can't follow what they said
당신은 그들이 말한 것을 따를 수 없습니다
banquet
연회
Just do as you say
그냥 네 말대로 해
Better wait a little longer
좀 더 기다려보는 게 좋을 거야
A new round of evaluation results?
새로운 평가 결과?
It seems
것 같다
I have to go there myself
내가 직접 거기로 가야 해